Leonardo Pérez

Cll 23 #41-70 Ap 712 Medellín, CO

I have a broad vision regarding all the software development process. My experience in different sectors of the industry allows me to create integral solutions that provide value to the process.

I am using following languages:

C/C#, Swift, Java, Kotlin, React Native, Flutter, ReactJS, NodeJS, AngularJS, VueJS, ElectronJS, PHP and their frameworks

Traits in development

As a good researcher, I will be able to solve the challenging problems.

My greatest strength is a combination of enthusiasm and persistence. I am able to persevere through challenges and setbacks without falling into frustration. I am very passionate about work and because of my high energy levels.

As a fast-learner, I am confident I can quickly learn what is required in the position and contribute to the team's objectives. My work ethic won't let me settle for less than my best.

If you hire me, I will put my best to achieve the goals of your team.

Hobbies and Interests: I like sports and music and in my free time, I enjoy gardening and hiking.

Open to work for any employer, and anywhere.

Technical Skills

Mobile App Development 10 years

- Swift, Objective-C, Kotlin, Java
- React native, Flutter, Ionic Framework, Xamarin, etc

Web App Development 10 years

- Front-end Development (React, Angular, Vue, PHP, Python)
- Back-end Development (Node, PHP, Python)

Work History

- DMS SAS / Lead developer

January 1999 - Sep 2004, Medellín - Colombia

Software solutions for the Automotive and retail industry in the Latin American market.

- Koala Solutions / Software developer

MONTH 2004 - Currently

This is my brand, I have develop software for more that 20 years in different sectors

- Plate Pros / iOS developer

July 2023 - August 2023 Hollywood, CA.

Created 360-degree camera app using Swift/SwiftUI, RealityKit, ARKit etc.

- Hutch Systems / Mobile developer

January 2023 - August 2023 Abbotsford, BC, Canada

Education

Tecnológico de Antioquia / Bachelor of technology

Jan 1993 - Dec 1995 Medellín - CO